http://www.pakor.com/pakor-privacy-information

My Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Commercial Proofing Paper
Epson Proofing Paper Standard (240)
Epson Proofing Paper Standard (205)
Epson Proofing Paper White Semimatte
Standard Proofing Paper Production (210)
HP Specialty Papers
HP Films (Technical & Graphic)
Pakor Gallery Wraps
Standard Bars - 1.25"
Pro Bars - 1.75"
Commercial Proofing Paper
Epson Proofing Paper Standard (240)
Epson Proofing Paper Standard (205)
Epson Proofing Paper White Semimatte
Standard Proofing Paper Production (210)
HP Specialty Papers
HP Films (Technical & Graphic)
Pakor Gallery Wraps
Standard Bars - 1.25"
Pro Bars - 1.75"
Privacy Policy
last updated December 1, 2016Pakor Inc. (Pakor)
PRIVACY POLICY: Your privacy is important to Pakor Inc. This privacy policy applies to the Pakor’s web sites sales and services and tells you how your personal information is collected, used, disclosed, and protected by Pakor.
CHANGES TO THIS POLICY: We may change this Policy from time to time. IF we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the "last updated" date above.
ORDERING:  Pakor respects your (User) privacy. When placing an order, User provides information including User's name, telephone number, email address, delivery address, as well as order recipient name, telephone number, email address and mailing address (Private Information). Pakor will not sell, barter, lease, rent, donate or share User's Private Information. Pakor will provide User's Private Information solely to enable fulfillment of User's order.
CREDIT CARD TRANSACTION PROCESSING: User authorizes Pakor to process payment for orders at the time orders are placed. This means User's credit card will be pre-authorized upon order and charged upon shipment.
NETWORK AND INFORMATION SECURITY: Pakor protects information we collect from you to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Highly confidential personal information such as credit card number and password that we request from you on our website is protected with Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology with 128-bit encryption. The servers on which information is stored are kept in a controlled environment with limited access. While we take reasonable efforts to guard personal information, no security system is impenetrable. Your account is accessible only through the use of an individual user ID and password. To protect the confidentiality of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused. In addition, always logout and close your browser when you finish your session. Please note that we will never ask you to disclose your password in an unsolicited phone call or email. User certifies that User is at least 18 years of age. Anyone under 18 years of age must have permission and accompaniment of an adult to use the site.
1-800-572-3600
store@pakor.com
Customer service
Terms and Conditions
Shipping & Returns
Contact us
New products
Recently viewed products
For more info on ourproducts and promotions.
Subscribe
Copyright © 2020 Pakor. All rights reserved.
|
Sitemap
Powered by nopCommerce
Sign up today to earn FREE SHIPPING!
